Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- RECORD GROUP B: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 202 SEATTLE, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-47/1, 69-73)
  - SERIES XI: CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS, 1892-1980 (Box-folder 26/1-41/22)
    - Vancouver Misc., 1973-1975 (Box-folder 40/27)
    - Warren, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 40/28)
    - Weyerhaeuser - TACOMA, 1975 (Box-folder 40/29)
    - Western Typographers, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/30)
    - Guild -TNG, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 40/31)
    - Guild - ITU,VDT,OCR,ETC, 1975 (Box-folder 40/32)
    - Guild - TNT, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 40/33)
    - Guild - P-I-TImes, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/34)
    - Snoqualmie Falls Record, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Higline times / contract, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - 1971 Negotiations (Newspaper) Part1, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - 1971 Negotiations (Newspaper) Part2, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Newspaper Proposal and Negotiations (Part 1), 1971 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Newspaper Proposal and Negotiations (Part 2), 1971 (Box-folder 41/6)
    - Newspaper Proposal and Negotiations (Part 3), 1971 (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Local Burger 1971 Negotiations (Part 1) (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Local Burger 1971 Negotiations (Part 2) (Box-folder 41/9)
    - News Publishing Company Agreement (Part 1), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 41/10)
    - News Publishing Company Agreement (Part 2), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 41/11)
    - News Publishing Company Agreement (Part 3), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 41/12)
    - News Publishing Company Agreement (Part 4), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 41/13)
    - Misc. Scales (Part 1), 1959-1969 (Box-folder 41/14)
    - Misc. Scales (Part 2), 1959-1969 (Box-folder 41/15)
    - Trade Typesetting, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 41/16)
    - Nego. Typehouse, 1972 (Box-folder 41/17)
    - Craftsman Press Negotiation, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 41/18)
    - Everett Emtract Appeal, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 41/19)
    - Snoqualmie, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 41/20)
    - Contracts Snoqualmie Valley Record, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 41/21)
    - Labor's supporting role in state, county and local civil defense, 1965 (Box-folder 41/22)
  - SERIES XII: MEMBERSHIP MATERIALS, 1890-1901 (Box-folder BOX 66)
    - Minutes and Roll Call Journal, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66 (Flat box))
    - Membership Journal of Seattle No.202, 1890-1901 (Box-folder 66 (Flat box))
    - International Membership Cards (London Society, South African, Sweden, New South Wales), 1890-1907 (Box-folder 66 (Flat box))
  - SERIES XIII: PUBLICATIONS, 1933, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 42/1-42/66)
    - Washington Public Service Employee (Newspaper), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Washington Newspaper Publication Association Rate Book, 1964 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Washington State Labor News, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Washington Teamster, 1965 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - West Seattle Herald, 1964 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - West Seattle World, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - The Washington Newspaper, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - The News, 1965 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - Washington Newspaper Publication Association Rate Book, 1965 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - Valu-Mart Flyer, 1965 (Box-folder 42/10)
    - University of Washington Daily, 1965 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - The United Way, 1963 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - Tacoma News Tribune, 1964 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - Seattle Printers' Lockout News, 1933 (Box-folder 42/14)
    - Sports and Play USA, 1963 (Box-folder 42/15)
    - The Shopper, 1964 (Box-folder 42/16)
    - Service Union Reporter, 1964 (Box-folder 42/17)
    - Seattle Magazine, 1964 (Box-folder 42/18)
    - Seattle School, 1964 (Box-folder 42/19)
    - Seafarer's Log, 1965 (Box-folder 42/20)
    - Rhodes Circular, 1964 (Box-folder 42/21)
    - The Retail Outlook, 1965 (Box-folder 42/22)
    - Republican Party Platform, 1964 (Box-folder 42/23)
    - Renton Town Talk, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 42/24)
    - The Ranger, 1964 (Box-folder 42/25)
    - Rainier District Times, 1964 (Box-folder 42/26)
    - Pictorial Reporter and North Tacoma News, 1963 (Box-folder 42/27)
    - Queen Anne News, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 42/28)
    - Puyallup Valley Tribune, 1964 (Box-folder 42/29)
    - Publisher's Auxiliary, 1964 (Box-folder 42/30)
    - Price Mart, 1963 (Box-folder 42/31)
    - Portland Reporter, 1964 (Box-folder 42/32)
    - Port Angeles Evening News, 1965 (Box-folder 42/33)
    - Parkland Times Journal, 1964 (Box-folder 42/34)
    - The Olympia Churchman, 1963 (Box-folder 42/35)
    - Oregon Labor Press, 1964 (Box-folder 42/36)
    - Offset Newspaper Publishing (Part1), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/37)
    - Offset Newspaper Publishing (Part2), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/38)
    - Offset Newspaper Publishing (Part3), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/39)
    - Northwest Pod News, 1964 (Box-folder 42/40)
    - Northwest Italian News, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/41)
    - Northshore Citizens, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 42/42)
    - Northshore News, 1966 (Box-folder 42/43)
    - Marysville Globe, 1963 (Box-folder 42/44)
    - Lynnwood Enterprise, 1963 (Box-folder 42/45)
    - Suburban Times, 1965 (Box-folder 42/46)
    - Lake city star, 1963 (Box-folder 42/47)
    - The Labor Journal, 1964 (Box-folder 42/48)
    - Kirkland East Side Journal, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 42/49)
    - East Side Journal, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/50)
    - Kent Independent Shopper, 1963 (Box-folder 42/51)
    - Hunting and fishing News, 1963 (Box-folder 42/52)
    - Guild Reporter, 1965 (Box-folder 42/53)
    - Guild Journal, 1964 (Box-folder 42/54)
    - The Cardinal, 1963 (Box-folder 42/55)
    - Federal way Tribune, 1964 (Box-folder 42/56)
    - The Facts, 1964 (Box-folder 42/57)
    - The Dagger Blade, 1963 (Box-folder 42/58)
    - Community News (Queen Anne and Magnolia area), 1963 (Box-folder 42/59)
    - Catholic Northwest Progress, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 42/60)
    - Joint Strike Ads, 1963 (Box-folder 42/61)
    - Burden guide Journal, 1965 (Box-folder 42/62)
    - Bainbridge review, 1964 (Box-folder 42/63)
    - The Bellevue American, 1964 (Box-folder 42/64)
    - The Argus, 1964 (Box-folder 42/65)
    - Aero Mechanic, 1965 (Box-folder 42/66)
  - SERIES XIV: COMMITTEE FILES, 1922-19657 (Box-folder 43/1-45/30)
    - Label Campaign, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - Label Promotion League, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Loans, 1931-1941 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - Northwest Printing Trades Federation, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Northwest Typographical Conference, 1927-1931 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Membership Comm. Reports, 1937-1955 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Membership Comm. Reports, 1922-1936 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - International Typographical Union (Part 1), 1931-1954 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - International Typographical Union (Part 2), 1931-1954 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - International Typographical Union (Part 3), 1931-1954 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Referendums, 1931-1949 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Political Action Comm., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - Secy's Supplemental Report, 1931-1935 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - Sanitation Comm, 1929-1948 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - News Shaw, A.L. (Discharge), 1958 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - Strike Job (Univ. Printing), 1958 (Box-folder 43/16)
    - Times Lockout Guild, 1953 (Box-folder 43/17)
    - Servicemen, 1942-1955 (Box-folder 43/18)
    - Newman Discharge Case, 1958 (Box-folder 43/19)
    - Hanson, HM, 1950 (Box-folder 43/20)
    - Special Standing Committee, 1956 (Box-folder 43/21)
    - News - Herald Hanson, 1958 (Box-folder 43/22)
    - Special Standing Committee (part 1), 1943-1954 (Box-folder 43/23)
    - Special Standing Committee (part 2), 1936-1942 (Box-folder 43/24)
    - Strike, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 43/25)
    - Strike P-I Guild Dispute, 1936 (Box-folder 43/26)
    - Old Reports Misc., 1932-1946 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Picnic Committee, 1951 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Offset Committe, 1955 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Old Apprentice Applications, 1925-1928 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Membership Committee, Misc., 1938-1959 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - Central Labor Council, 1957 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Couthard vs. Winans, 1928 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - Winans vs. 202, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 44/8)
    - Secy Randolph - $15,000 Loan, 1934 (Box-folder 44/9)
    - Defense Work, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - ITU Delegates Misc., 1924-1958 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - Economy Committee, 1950 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Sanitation Committee, 1953 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - Bureau of Education, 1925-1948 (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Entertainment Committee, 1934-1950 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Coordinating Committee, 1952 (Box-folder 44/16)
    - Co-op Committee, 1951 (Box-folder 44/17)
    - Chapel Notices, 1940-1958 (Box-folder 44/18)
    - Convention Committee, 1950-1958 (Box-folder 44/19)
    - Donations, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 44/20)
    - Monthly Letters (part 1), 1947-1952 (Box-folder 44/21)
    - Monthly Letters (part 2), 1953-1959 (Box-folder 44/22)
    - Thermo - FAX, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Typing applications, 1958 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Apprentice Typing, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - 106th convention, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - 104th convention, 1962 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - 103rd convention, 1961 (Box-folder 45/6)
    - 102nd convention, 1960 (Box-folder 45/7)
    - Apprentice record, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 45/8)
    - 80th anniversary celebration, 1962 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - Dues-old, 1950-1962 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - UNIT IV TESTS, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - J.D. byler appeal, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 45/12)
    - Highline Times Appeal, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 45/13)
    - J Goodwyn vs. J D Byler, 1957 (Box-folder 45/14)
    - Greenlee, Clyde. Discipline Com-charges- Appeal andrebuttal, 1965 (Box-folder 45/15)
    - STU vs. EDW Clark, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 45/16)
    - Loans-old, 1941-1952 (Box-folder 45/17)
    - Special Committees, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 45/18)
    - STU vs. WM Schreven, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 45/19)
    - Seattle Newspaper Guild, 1936-1948 (Box-folder 45/20)
    - Reproduction, 1962 (Box-folder 45/21)
    - Washington State labor council, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 45/22)
    - Resolutions, 1936-1947 (Box-folder 45/23)
    - Representatives in govt, 1934-1949 (Box-folder 45/24)
    - Trustees, 1938-1954 (Box-folder 45/25)
    - Reports of committees1936-1943 (Box-folder 45/26)
    - Executive Comm. Misc, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 45/27)
    - ITU SEC. HURD #1, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 45/28)
    - ITU PRES. RANDOLPH (Part1), 1947-1958 (Box-folder 45/29)
    - ITU PRES. RANDOLPH (Part2), 1947-1958 (Box-folder 45/30)
  - SERIES XV: SCRAPBOOKS AND CLIPPINGS, 1933, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 46/1-46/16)
    - Clippings, 1882-1887 (Box-folder 46/1)
    - 202 labor temple, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - The Ideal Scrap Book (part 1), 1929-1933 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - The Ideal Scrap Book (part 2), 1929-1933 (Box-folder 46/4)
    - By-Laws, 1882-1953 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - New Laws and By Laws Change, 1955 (Box-folder 46/6)
    - Union Label Campaign, 1948 (Box-folder 46/7)
    - Constitution By-Laws and rules of order, 1961 (Box-folder 46/8)
    - Commercial Agreement, 1963 (Box-folder 46/9)
    - Citizen job protection,- newspaper, agreement, etc, 1965 (Box-folder 46/10)
    - Strikebreakers, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 46/11)
    - pictures of Seattle typographical union, 1968 (Box-folder 46/12)
    - Fidelity Magnetic Tape, 1957 (Box-folder 46/13)
    - #202 Seattle washington newspaper, 1917-1948 (Box-folder 46/14)
    - #202 Seattle washington newspaper (Part2), 1917-1948 (Box-folder 46/15)
    - Job applicants, 1965 (Box-folder 46/16)
  - SERIES XVI: GENERAL LEDGER, 1948-197965 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - Financial Record Logbook, 1948-1979 (Box-folder 47/1)
  - SERIES XVII: DUES LEDGER, 1911-1961 (Box-folder 69/1-73/1)
    - Dues Ledger for Members of Seattle Typographical Union No. 202 (Part 1 of 5), 1911-1926 (Box-folder 69/1 (oversized))
    - Dues Ledger for Members of Seattle Typographical Union No. 202 (Part 2 of 5), 1926-1940 (Box-folder 70/1 (oversized))
    - Dues Ledger for Members of Seattle Typographical Union No. 202 (Part 3 of 5), 1940-1952 (Box-folder 71/1 (oversized))
    - Dues Ledger for Members of Seattle Typographical Union No. 202 (Part 4 of 5), 1952-1957 (Box-folder 72/1 (oversized))
    - Dues Ledger for Members of Seattle Typographical Union No. 202 (Part 5 of 5), 1958-1961 (Box-folder 73/1 (oversized))
- RECORD GROUP C: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 170 TACOMA, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 48/1-Box 57, 67/1)
  - SERIES I: ORGANIZATION, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 48/1, 48/24)
    - President's file, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Constitution ByLaws and Rules of Order, Undated (Box-folder 48/24)
  - SERIES II: CORRESPONDENCE AND SUBJECT FILES, 1883-1979 (Box-folder 48/2-48/23, 48/25-49/36)
    - Picnic Tickets, 1963 (Box-folder 48/2)
    - Picnic, 1967 (Box-folder 48/3)
    - Picnic, 1965 (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Washington conference of typo unions, Banquets, 1883-1963 (Box-folder 48/5)
    - Conference WTC, 1956 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - OCR-negotitations, 1973 (Box-folder 48/7)
    - Typographical Contract, 1969 (Box-folder 48/8)
    - Merger- Seattle Typographical Union-Tacoma Typographical Union, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 48/9)
    - Typographical Union No.170, 1971 (Box-folder 48/10)
    - Local Union Equal Employment Opportunity Report EEO-3, 1967 (Box-folder 48/11)
    - Tacoma Typographical Union No.170, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 48/12)
    - Central Labor Council, 1973 (Box-folder 48/13)
    - ITU Convention Delegate, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 48/14)
    - Members of T.T.U No.170, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48/15)
    - Tacoma Typographical Union No.170-writing, 1903 (Box-folder 48/16)
    - ITU Convention, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 48/17)
    - signatures of members of 170, Undated (Box-folder 48/18)
    - Amnesty, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 48/19)
    - Overtime Fine, 1969 (Box-folder 48/20)
    - Appeals, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 48/21)
    - Washington State Labor Council (Part 1), 1963-1971 (Box-folder 48/22)
    - Washington State Labor Council (Part 2), 1952-1965 (Box-folder 48/23)
    - Washington State Typograpical court, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 48/25)
    - Welfare, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48/26)
    - Congress of the U.S., 1957-1970 (Box-folder 48/27)
    - Tacoma Recreation and open space plan, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 48/28)
    - International Typograpical Union, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 48/29)
    - AFL-CIO, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 48/30)
    - Everett Sauve, 1967 (Box-folder 48/31)
    - Sanitation, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 48/32)
    - ITU Ruling Table, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 48/33)
    - Western Union, 1962 (Box-folder 48/34)
    - Financial Reports, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 48/35)
    - Annual Salmon Derby, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 48/36)
    - Bowling, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 48/37)
    - Baseball, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 48/38)
    - Elections, 1967 (Box-folder 48/39)
    - NW Progressive Club, 1966 (Box-folder 48/40)
    - Mediation, 1967 (Box-folder 48/41)
    - Typographical Scale, 1936-1958 (Box-folder 48/42)
    - Merger Report, 1974 (Box-folder 48/43)
    - Committee Reports, 1974 (Box-folder 48/44)
    - Secretary Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 48/45)
    - Committee Reports, 1922-1959 (Box-folder 48/46)
    - General Correspondence, 1938-1962 (Box-folder 48/47)
    - General Correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 48/48)
    - Organization Correspondence, 1918 (Box-folder 48/49)
    - General Correspondence, 1913-1917 (Box-folder 48/50)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box-folder 49/1)
    - Hay vs. Redmond, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 49/2)
    - Arbitration, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 49/3)
    - Strike, 1952 (Box-folder 49/4)
    - Tribune Strike, 1952 (Box-folder 49/5)
    - Strike Reports, 1952 (Box-folder 49/6)
    - Lakewood, 1962 (Box-folder 49/7)
    - Pioneer Lockout, 1964 (Box-folder 49/8)
    - Job Contract Negotiations, 1967 (Box-folder 49/9)
    - Meeting /w Howard Reed, 1963 (Box-folder 49/10)
    - Federal Way Notices, 1964 (Box-folder 49/11)
    - Auburn Citizen, Inc. Legal Papers, 1962 (Box-folder 49/12)
    - Auburn Citizen, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 49/13)
    - Puyallup, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 49/14)
    - Auburn Citizen matter only, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 49/15)
    - Suburban Times NIRB suit against allied, Pressmen 49, TTU 170, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 49/16)
    - Progressive Campaign Committee, 1966 (Box-folder 49/17)
    - Hand bills, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 49/18)
    - Organizational Manual, Undated (Box-folder 49/19)
    - Pioneer Info. Program, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 49/20)
    - Portland-Oregon Report, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 49/21)
    - Monthly News Letters, 1967 (Box-folder 49/22)
    - Mutual AIO, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/23)
    - Mutual Aid Reports, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 49/24)
    - Monthly Letters, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 49/25)
    - Oregon-Northwest Mutual Aid Pact, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 49/26)
    - Audit Reports, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 49/27)
    - Financial Reporting Kit, 1961 (Box-folder 49/28)
    - Tacoma Report, 1952 (Box-folder 49/29)
    - Representative, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 49/30)
    - Tacoma Typographical Union, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 49/31)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondences, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 49/32)
    - Portland Reporter, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 49/33)
    - Puyallup Valley Tribune Letters, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 49/34)
    - National Labor Relations Board Letters, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 49/35)
    - Washington State Mutual Circle, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 49/36)
  - SERIES III: MINUTES, 1883-1974 (Box-folder 50/1-51/2)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1883-1887 (Box-folder 50/1)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1906-1910 (Box-folder 50/2)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1910-1913 (Box-folder 50/3)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1913-1916 (Box-folder 50/4)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1917 (Box-folder 50/5)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1918 (Box-folder 50/6)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1919 (Box-folder 50/7)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1919-1921 (Box-folder 50/8)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 50/9)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1922-1934 (Box-folder 50/10)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1934 (Box-folder 50/11)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1935 (Box-folder 50/12)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 50/13)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 50/14)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 50/15)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1942 (Box-folder 50/16)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 50/17)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 50/18)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 50/19)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 50/20)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 50/21)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 50/22)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 50/23)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 50/24)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 50/25)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 50/26)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1952 (Box-folder 50/27)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1952 (Box-folder 50/28)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1952 (Box-folder 50/29)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1952 (Box-folder 50/30)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1953 (Box-folder 50/31)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1953 (Box-folder 50/32)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1953 (Box-folder 50/33)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1954 (Box-folder 50/34)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1955 (Box-folder 50/35)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1956 (Box-folder 50/36)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1957 (Box-folder 50/37)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1958 (Box-folder 50/38)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1959 (Box-folder 50/39)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 50/40)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 50/41)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1961 (Box-folder 50/42)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1962 (Box-folder 50/43)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1962 (Box-folder 50/44)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1963 (Box-folder 50/45)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1963 (Box-folder 50/46)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1964 (Box-folder 50/47)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1965 (Box-folder 50/48)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1965 (Box-folder 50/49)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1966 (Box-folder 50/50)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1967 (Box-folder 50/51)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1968 (Box-folder 50/52)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1969 (Box-folder 50/53)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1970 (Box-folder 50/54)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 50/55)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 50/56)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 51/1)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 51/2)
  - SERIES IV: MINUTES - EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1913-1969 (Box-folder 51/3-52/37)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1951 (Box-folder 51/3)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1952 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1953 (Box-folder 51/5)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1954 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1955 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1956 (Box-folder 51/8)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1957 (Box-folder 51/9)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1958 (Box-folder 51/10)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1959 (Box-folder 51/11)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 51/12)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, Undated (Box-folder 51/13)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1913 (Box-folder 52/1)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1914 (Box-folder 52/2)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1915 (Box-folder 52/3)